Kettle and Idol
Now then, this kettle of fish, the main project.
Yes, sir!
Please give me a cute title ball.
Yes, sir.
My third element
Yay!
Yes.
Today is the third element.
Well, this was supposed to be the third element, but I was too lenient.
But I was too lenient, so it's okay. Let's make it the third element this time.
Wait a minute. I just said the third element.
You said it so sweetly and seriously that I'm making it the third element of this show.
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's fine. It's fine.
The three main elements.
I'll go with the third element.
Let's go with the "trifecta".
This time, we'll go with the trifecta.
Okay, let's see.
Let's hear your trifecta.
Here are my three main elements.
Number one is family.
Family
Number two, exercise.
Exercise.
And number three is eight o'clock.
That's a good story.
Yes, sir.
My family, I have four brothers and sisters,
Oh, you really have?
Yes, I do. And the closest one is 8 years older than me,
The older one?
Yes. I have three older ones, two older sisters and an older brother,
The furthest one is 12 years old. That's one year apart,
Oh, wow!
Wow, I don't know, they are adults, and their clothes are so cute,
Oh!
I often borrow clothes from them,
I'm probably, you know, when I'm posting on Instagram or something,
I also ask them to check if the text is correct,
And also, the photos for Instagram.
I, um, I had never done it before,
I didn't even know how to post my instagrams,
So, my three older siblings taught me how to do it,
They gave me a lot of advice, like, "You should take pictures like this.
Oh, I see.
Yes, that's right.
By the way, do you have any episodes of going somewhere with your family recently?
Well, I posted it on my Instagram,
Recently, I went with my oldest sister who is 12 years older than me,
I went on an outing with my oldest sister, who is 12 years older than me, and my brother, who is 10 years older than me,
We had a really fancy lunch together,
What's that?
Yeah, and we took pictures, just because,
I asked her to take a picture for my Instagram,
I'm not very good at taking pictures of people in their natural state,
I'm not very good at taking natural-looking pictures, so when I hold out the camera, I get all poised.
When I get the camera out, I tend to get a weird smile on my face,
So, I wanted to make my smile a little more natural,
So I took pictures with her pointing out to me how to smile more naturally.
You are a producer, aren't you, Ms. Nami?
That's right.
You must have a lot of wonderful producers in your family.
Yes, they really help me out.
I see.
I see. So, when you joined Ebichu,
And when you entered Ebichu, did you and your older sister talk with each other?
Did it come naturally to you?
Is that different?
Oh, but I think I was able to talk with her without being nervous.
I see.
Yes, I think so.
I would like to try out for an athletic meet. A relay.
I would like to see that.
Yes, I would.
I would like to see this program.
Mao-chan
Tomoki-san
Mr. Monta Monta
Mr. Shrimp
Mr. Ren provided this program.
Thank you very much!